<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Hawaii Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Hawaii Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Who We Are The Chapter is a voluntary organization of over 300 members in private, group, military and academic practice as well as pediatricians in training and other non-pediatric physicians interested in Child Health issues.
What We Stand For The mission of the Hawaii Chapter is to attain optimal physical, mental and social health and well-being for infants, children, adolescents and young adults. We will accomplish this mission by addressing the needs of children, their families and their communities, and by supporting Chapter members through advocacy, education, research, service and improving the systems through which they deliver pediatric care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advocacy</title>
      <link>/advocacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advocacy/</guid>
      <description>Advocacy HAAP is actively examining the needs of the children we treat as well as the needs of the pediatricians in our community. We have sought to establish dialogue and credibility with those that set health care policy.
Active Issues The AAP Section on Tobacco Control Executive Committee for Health Affairs Blog
Articles Don’t Be Silent About Protecting Sleeping Infants From Harm (StarAdvertiser: PDF)
Mandatory Reporting for Children Who are Suspected of Being Victims of Sex and/or Labor Trafficking From The Honorable Karen M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/</guid>
      <description>CONTINUING MEDICAL EDUCATION Timely Topics in Pediatrics April 4, 2019 – 11:30 to 5:45 pm Ala Moana Hotel This activity has been planned and implemented in accordance with the Accreditation Requirements and Policies of the Kansas Medical Society through the joint providership of Kansas Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics and the American Academy of Pediatrics, Hawaii Chapter.
Kansas Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics is accredited by the Kansas Medical Society to provide continuing medical education for physicians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSV</title>
      <link>/rsv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rsv/</guid>
      <description>RSV Guidelines The following PDF document is the Guidelines for Prophylaxis for RSV Infections in High-Risk Infants in Hawaii which is developed by the Consensus Committee, which is comprised of neonatologists, pediatricians, hospitalists, pediatric intensivists, pediatric specialists, and insurance representatives from various hospital and medical groups on Oahu and the neighbor islands every year prior to the RSV season.
This committee also welcomes comments from community pediatricians and other healthcare providers regarding RSV infections in their practices and the impact of these guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Resources EHDI Epress Newsletter EHDI Express September – 2017
EHDI Express November – 2017
EHDI Express JANUARY 2018
HPV Vaccine Video for Health Care Providers MDH has created a 12-minute video for health care providers on HPV vaccine communication. The video begins with humorous vignettes and then presents four model clinical encounters in which providers demonstrate low-stress ways of recommending HPV vaccine and answering questions from patients and parents. Each of the model encounters can also be viewed individually.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>